# This is the part where I explain my idea
My family is very much into watching football and following our family favorite team Manchester United. The thing is is that they talk so much about players coming in and out and how well they are and what positions they work best in that I get really lost and it is really hard to follow. I plan on using my project to analyze these players and see who really does perform well and who people really just only says play well. Sometimes they talk about statistics on the sports shows but they are really watered down. 

I plan on using data that has been collected into CSV filled on the players and matches for particular seasons. I am unsure which season I want to analyze because the current one's data is not yet finished so I might look at last years. The data I have already looked at has many things such as Name, age, position, club, minutes played, wins, losses, nationality, appearances, shots and all stuff like that.
