1. 1. Are any of your predicted response values from your best model scientifically meaningless? Explain.

1. With some of the predictions yes but others are feasible. For example you can forever increase the amount of nitrogen but for others like light there is only so much light that can be added before you can't add any more or any longer or scientifically once a temperature becomes too high we wouldn't see that in normal nature and it would end up just burning the test. Kind of like the car example of predicting a zero cylinder engine it doesn't work because it's not physically possible. 

1. 2. In your plots, did you find any non-linear relationships? Do a bit of research online and give a link to at least one resource explaining how to deal with modeling 
2. 		non-linear relationships in R. 


1. The plot that I made with the relationship between growth rate and nitrogen actually turned out to be more of a bell curve where adding too much actually inhibited growth.  I found this article online that talked a bit about it. https://techvidvan.com/tutorials/nonlinear-regression-in-r/

1. 3. Write the code you would use to model the data found in "/Data/non_linear_relationship.csv" with a linear model (there are a few ways of doing this)
2. 
3. Df <- read_csv("./Data/non_linear_relationship.csv")
4. 
5. Model <- nls(data = Df, formula = response ~ predictor)
6. 		

